<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Marco Salazar</title><link>https://marsalal.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Marco Salazar</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us, es-es</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marsalal.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2021 Highlights</title><link>https://marsalal.github.io/post/2021-highlights/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marsalal.github.io/post/2021-highlights/</guid><description>This 2021 year has been both special and somehow bitter for me, which I guess its something that most of you could relate. I&amp;rsquo;ve always believe that not all the time you can have good times and good experiences, even if it happens for a long time eventually something wont come out as you expect and you need to accept it. So, lets start with what went bad/not-expected/dissapointing things
The bad things Month What sucked?</description></item><item><title>How &amp; why I created this site?</title><link>https://marsalal.github.io/post/how-i-created-site/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marsalal.github.io/post/how-i-created-site/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always thought that having a personal website will make you stand up above the rest of the people, lets admit it, having a site may add an extra hours in front of the desk and it will most likely will need a few pennys to maintain it. If you are not a developer or someone with the extra curiosity to learn by yourself; its highly probable that you either dont do it or dont want to hire someone to do it for you.</description></item><item><title>Our 2021 marathon journey</title><link>https://marsalal.github.io/post/chicago-marathon-2021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marsalal.github.io/post/chicago-marathon-2021/</guid><description>My journey to complete a marathon in 2021 was planned in a very different way than it tuned out to be, it all began during April 2021 when the Rotterdam organization said that a full in-person marathon was going to take place in October 24th, 2021. That was a big motivation after what happened in March 2020 and then in October 2020, if you add the possibility of having vaccinated, our chances to go to the Netherlands and run the marathon have increased a LOT!</description></item><item><title>Who am I?</title><link>https://marsalal.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marsalal.github.io/about/</guid><description>Software developer with more than 12+ years of experience; I have had the opportunity to work in almost all spectre of an application: mobile, web &amp;amp; back-end. Most of the time I have spent has been in back-end projects where C# and .Net technologies have been my specialities.
Also I have performed as tech lead for small and multi-region teams with different seniorities, always looking to increase the potential of each member and to reach the team&amp;rsquo;s goals.</description></item></channel></rss>